export const difficultyType = [
  {
    level: 'easy',
    category: [
      {
        type: 'history',
        questions: [
          {
            question: 'Afghanistan in which year got its independance from history 1',
            answers: [1929, 1919, 1928, 1993],
            correctAnswer: 1919,
          },

          {
            question: 'How much does Afghanistan has provinces from history 2',
            answers: [34, 33, 32, 35],
            correctAnswer: 34,
          },
          {
            question: 'What is the Capital of Afghanistan from history 3',
            answers: ['Herat', 'Mazar', 'logar', 'Kabul'],
            correctAnswer: 'Kabul',
          },
          {
            question: 'What is the Capital of Afghanistan from history 4',
            answers: ['Herat', 'Mazar', 'logar', 'Kabul'],
            correctAnswer: 'Kabul',
          },
          {
            question: 'What is the Capital of Afghanistan from history 5',
            answers: ['Herat', 'Mazar', 'logar', 'Kabul'],
            correctAnswer: 'Kabul',
          },
        ],
      },
      // 0.history.q1.question

      {
        type: 'sports',
        questions: [
          {
            question: 'Afghanistan in which year got its independance from sports',
            answers: [1929, 1919, 1928, 1993],
            correctAnswer: 1919,
          },
          {
            question: 'How much does Afghanistan has provinces from sports',
            answers: [34, 33, 32, 35],
            correctAnswer: 34,
          },
          {
            question: 'What is the Capital of Afghanistan from sports',
            answers: ['Herat', 'Mazar', 'logar', 'Kabul'],
            correctAnswer: 'Kabul',
          },
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
]

// export const medium = [
//   {
//     history: {
//       q1: {
//         question: 'Afghanistan in which year got its independance in medium from history',
//         answers: [1929, 1919, 1928, 1993],
//         correctAnswer: 1,
//       },
//       q2: {
//         question: 'How much does Afghanistan has provinces in medium from history',
//         answers: [34, 33, 32, 35],
//         correctAnswer: 0,
//       },
//       q3: {
//         question: 'What is the Capital of Afghanistan in medium from history',
//         answers: ['Herat', 'Mazar', 'logar', 'Kabul'],
//         correctAnswer: 3,
//       },
//     },
//     sports: {
//       q1: {
//         question: 'Afghanistan in which year got its independance in medium from sports',
//         answers: [1929, 1919, 1928, 1993],
//         correctAnswer: 1,
//       },
//       q2: {
//         question: 'How much does Afghanistan has provinces in medium from sports',
//         answers: [34, 33, 32, 35],
//         correctAnswer: 0,
//       },
//       q3: {
//         question: 'What is the Capital of Afghanistan in medium from sports',
//         answers: ['Herat', 'Mazar', 'logar', 'Kabul'],
//         correctAnswer: 3,
//       },
//     },
//   },
// ]

// export const hard = [
//   {
//     history: {
//       q1: {
//         question: 'Afghanistan in which year got its independance in hard from history',
//         answers: [1929, 1919, 1928, 1993],
//         correctAnswer: 1,
//       },
//       q2: {
//         question: 'How much does Afghanistan has provinces in hard from history',
//         answers: [34, 33, 32, 35],
//         correctAnswer: 0,
//       },
//       q3: {
//         question: 'What is the Capital of Afghanistan in hard from history',
//         answers: ['Herat', 'Mazar', 'logar', 'Kabul'],
//         correctAnswer: 3,
//       },
//     },

//     sports: {
//       q1: {
//         question: 'Afghanistan in which year got its independance in hard from sports',
//         answers: [1929, 1919, 1928, 1993],
//         correctAnswer: 1,
//       },
//       q2: {
//         question: 'How much does Afghanistan has provinces in hard from sports',
//         answers: [34, 33, 32, 35],
//         correctAnswer: 0,
//       },
//       q3: {
//         question: 'What is the Capital of Afghanistan in hard from sports',
//         answers: ['Herat', 'Mazar', 'logar', 'Kabul'],
//         correctAnswer: 3,
//       },
//     },
//   },
// ]
